The Amanda Seals Show.
The Amanda Seals Show, it's Amanda Seals here.
We are joined by our headliner of the week,
comedian, actor, producer, writer,
hilarious person, good friend, Sydney Castillo,
who also is mean behind the grill.
What song reminds you of the good old Quincy days
when Quincy, you know, was coming into his own,
you know, turned that corner.
The girls was like, oh, you're cute.
Can we talk Tevin Campbell?
Really?
Can we talk Tevin Campbell,
or I would say Joe's first album,
or I would say like a case,
not just these are my favorite artists.
I knew it, I knew it, I knew it.
Faded pictures.
It's like, it's, it's like.
Dog, all that, it's like that,
that energy is when I was like going to date.
Like you was just, I was in my bag of like finding myself
as a man, a young man, like.
Any Drew Hill in there?
Tell me what you want.
I love Drew Hill.
Any of that, any of that?
Because I could see you doing the dance in the mirror
before you left the house.
First album, song number 10 is my favorite ever by Drew Hill.
Beauty? No, that's an album too.
That's the second album.
It's so special.
Your love is so special.
Amanda?
Love is so special.
Seasons tell it all.
If I could sing all.
Oh.
In a special way.
Sorry, sum, da-da-doo.
All right.
Not the scatting.
Scat-a-m-dee-sum, da-da-doo.
All right, last one.
What song describes your last relationship?
Hit him up.
About two parts.
No.
I'm not the scatting.